Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Nasri Fuleihan Collection
Circa 1910s - 1930s
Circa 1910s - 1940s
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
O'Keefe Edson, Gail
Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman
AD.MC.056
384 Photographic Prints 366 digital surrogates of gelatin silver photographs, with an additional 29 images from photography studios, letterheads and a copy of Fuleihan's British passport (395 images total).
The Nasri Fuleihan collection includes approximately 366 photographs, most of which were taken during Fuleihan's stay in Palestine from the late 1910s until 1924. In addition to photographs of Palestinian cities and towns, the collection reflects the use Fuleihan made of the camera in his daily work as an engineer (mostly in southern Palestine). The collection also documents the daily life of the workers involved in the infrastructure projects Fuleihan was involved in. Some of Fuleihan's photographs were inspired by the works of other photographers who operated in Palestine at the time, most notably the renowned Palestinian photographer Khalil Ra'd, whose studio in Jerusalem Fuleihan apparently visited. The collection also includes business cards of several photography studios in Palestine, Egypt and the United States, whose services Fuleihan used as well as a copy of his passport. Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan (or Nasri Fulayhan) (Born in 1891 in Nicosia, Cyprus; died in July 1959 in Bronxville, NY) was a Cypriot of Lebanese descent who studied civil engineering at Purdue University. After his graduation in 1912, Fuleihan traveled to Palestine where he was employed as an engineer by the Levant Producing Company and later by Standard Oil until 1924, when he returned to the United States. Fuleihan stayed in Palestine from the late 1910s until 1924. Text from the New York Times obituary dated 30 July 1959: "Nasri Fuleihan, a civil engineer associated with many projects in the metropolitain area. died Tuesday in St. Luke's Hospital after a long illness. He was 66 years old and resided at 15 Meadow Avenue, Bronxville, N. Y. Mr Fuleihan, who was born in Cyprus, graduated from Purdue University in 1912. He was one of a small group of engineers who pioneered in the prospecting for oil in the Middle East before World War I. Upon his return to this country, Mr. Fuleihan participated in the construction of the Holland Tunnel and the George Washington Bridge. Later he was with the realty firm of Webb and Knapp. He leaves his wife, isabel; a son, Neville, and a daughter, Mrs. Francis O'Keefe." https://www.nytimes.com/1959/07/30/archives/nasri-fuleihan.html
Object 056 Digital Copy Only
Content Description
The Nasri Fuleihan collection includes approximately 366 photographs, most of which were taken during Fuleihan's stay in Palestine from the late 1910s until 1924. In addition to photographs of Palestinian cities and towns, the collection reflects the use Fuleihan made of the camera in his daily work as an engineer (mostly in southern Palestine). The collection also documents the daily life of the workers involved in the infrastructure projects Fuleihan was involved in. Some of Fuleihan's photographs were inspired by the works of other photographers who operated in Palestine at the time, most notably the renowned Palestinian photographer Khalil Ra'd, whose studio in Jerusalem Fuleihan apparently visited. The collection also includes business cards of several photography studios in Palestine, Egypt and the United States, whose services Fuleihan used as well as a copy of his passport.
Biographical / Historical
Nasri Fuleihan (or Nasri Fulayhan, born 16th November 1891, was a Cypriot of Lebanese descent who studied engineering at Purdue University, graduating in 1912. After his graduation, Fuleihan traveled to Palestine where he was employed as a civil engineer by the Ottoman and, later, British authorities. Fuleihan stayed in Palestine from the late 1910s through the early/mid-1920s.
Fuleihan married Isabel Oussani, the daughter of Margaret Shea and Joseph Oussani, in 1925. They had two children, Dorothy and Neville Fuleihan. The Oussani-Fuleihan Family Collection containing 218 documents and 920 photographs has been cataloged and digitized at the Moise A. Khayrallah Center for Lebanese Diaspora Studies at NC State University. The Oussani-Fuleihan Family Collection - https://lebanesestudies.omeka.chass.ncsu.edu/collections/show/103
Text from the New York Times obituary dated 30 July 1959: "Nasri Fuleihan, a civil engineer associated with many projects in the metropolitain area. died Tuesday in St. Luke's Hospital after a long illness. He was 66 years old and resided at 15 Meadow Avenue, Bronxville, N. Y. Mr Fuleihan, who was born in Cyprus, graduated from Purdue University in 1912. He was one of a small group of engineers who pioneered in the prospecting for oil in the Middle East before World War I. Upon his return to this country, Mr. Fuleihan participated in the construction of the Holland Tunnel and the George Washington Bridge. Later he was with the realty firm of Webb and Knapp. He leaves his wife, isabel; a son, Neville, and a daughter, Mrs. Francis O'Keefe." https://www.nytimes.com/1959/07/30/archives/nasri-fuleihan.html
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Palestine; Photographic Prints; Civil Engineering; Jordan; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; North America; Bridges; O'Keefe Edson, Gail
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan passport
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (1/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000001; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (2/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000002; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; English Writing; Postal Stamps; French Writing; Printed Materials; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (3/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000003; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Photographic Prints; Palestine; Jerusalem; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Men
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (4/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000004; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Visas; New York, USA; Cairo, Egypt; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (5/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000005; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; Postal Stamps; Visas; French Writing; United States of America; Alexandria, Egypt; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (6/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000006; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Visas; Palestine; Jerusalem
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (7/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000007; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      English Writing; Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; Postal Stamps; Arabic Writing; Visas; Suez, Egypt; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (8/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000008; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Passport/ID card; Printed Materials; English Writing; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Visas; Palestine; Alexandria, Egypt; France; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (9/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000009; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (10/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000010; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      English Writing; Printed Materials; Passport/ID card; Postal Stamps; Visas; Jerusalem; Palestine
    - British passport belonging to Nasri Suleiman Fuleihan, issued from Jerusalem on the 30 January 1924 (11/11)., 30th January 1924; ref447_000011; 1 Photographic Prints; - (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      English Writing; Printed Materials; Passport/ID card; Postal Stamps; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa, Circa 1917 - 1922
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Men in Ottoman uniforms standing behind a crowd of people., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref335b; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 X 4.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Fez/Tarboush; Canes/Walking Sticks; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits; Hats
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Crowd of people near Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref336; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Crowds; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Horses; Military/Soldiers; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Religious Ceremony; Flags; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Soldiers walking alongside the Jerusalem Citadel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref345; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Shops; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Crowds of people alongside the Jerusalem Citadel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref348; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Shops; Signs/Signposts; English Writing; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Religious Ceremony; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Crowds of people alongside the Jerusalem Citadel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref349; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Shops; Signs/Signposts; English Writing; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Men in Ottoman uniforms overlooking a crowd., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref368; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Men; Women; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Fez/Tarboush; Boys; Children; Umbrellas/Parasols; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Religious Ceremony; Group Portraits; Hats
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel (taken from the roof of Amdursky's Hotel)., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref374; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Crowds; Palestine; Hotels; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel and Jaffa Gate., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref375; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Religious Ceremony; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref394; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 5.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Flags; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref395; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel and Jaffa Gate (taken from the roof of Amdursky's Hotel), Circa 1917 - 1922; ref393; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Horses; Animals; Religious Ceremony; Palestine; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A man overlooking a crowd of people in by the Jerusalem Citadel from the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref396; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Men; Crowds; Hats; Palestine; Hotels; Parades/Processions; Religious Ceremony; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel taken from the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref397; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 X 4.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Palestine; Hotels; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel, with men in uniforms in the background., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref398; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Signs/Signposts; English Writing; Military/Soldiers; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Shops; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel taken from the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref405; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Crowds; Shops; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - A crowd by the Jerusalem Citadel taken from the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref413; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Crowds; Men; Women; Buildings; Horses; Animals; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Flags; Group Portraits
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa - Men in uniforms on horseback in front of a crowd by Jaffa Gate, taken from the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref121; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Crowds; Men; Horses; Group Portraits; Animals; Buildings; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Religious Ceremony; Parades/Processions; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Jerusalem
    - Mawsim al-Nabi Musa? - People walking by the Jerusalem Citadel and Jaffa Gate, shop signs include one for Andre Terzis & Fils., Circa 1917 - 1922; ref217; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Shops; Men; Regional/National Dress; Camels; Animals; Signs/Signposts; English Writing; Clocks/Watches; Palestine; Group Portraits; Turbans
  - Three men and two women posing by a waterfall (linked refs 2, 3, 4, 5)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref1; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 13 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Women; Photographic Prints; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Waterfalls; Bow Ties; Unknown Locations
  - A stone bridge over a stream (linked refs 1, 3, 4, 5)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref2; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 11.5 X 8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Water; Countryside/Rural; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Landscapes
  - Three men and a woman sitting on a balcony in front of a river and stone bridge, with a building and mountain in the background (linked refs 1, 2, 4, 5)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref3; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Buildings; Bridges; Mountains/Hills; Countryside/Rural; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Restaurants/bars
  - A stone bridge over a stream (linked refs 1, 2, 3, 5)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref4; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 8.4 x 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Water; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Unknown Locations
  - A closeup of a stone bridge with a person posing in front of a balcony on the left (linked refs 1, 2, 3, 4)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref5; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 13 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Women; Individual Portraits; Bridges; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Water; Countryside/Rural
  - A body of water between mountains (linked ref7)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref6; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 11.2 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills; Water; Unknown Locations; Landscapes
  - A body of water between mountains (linked ref6)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref7; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 11 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Landscapes
  - People walking on a bridge over a river, with a second bridge in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref8; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 9.5 x 11.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Men; Women; Water; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - Two men on the edge of a train track., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref9; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 11.5 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Railways; Transportation; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America
  - Portrait of two men wearing bowler hats sitting on steps in front of a building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref10; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; North America
  - An incomplete metal bridge above a body of water, with smoke coming out of factory chimneys in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref11; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Water; Factories; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America
  - A train crossing a bridge over a river., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref12; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Trains; Railways; Transportation; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills; Water; Bridges; Rivers; North America
  - Two men sitting on a cliffside., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref13; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Group Portraits; Men; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Unknown Locations
  - A train in front of Sudbury station, Ontario., Circa 1910 - 1926; ref14; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Trains; Railways; Transportation; Buildings; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ontario, Canada; Street Lamps
  - A man standing on train tracks in front of Dominion Express Co. building at Sudbury station, Ontario., Circa 1910 - 1926; ref15; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Buildings; Men; Railways; Transportation; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ontario, Canada; Street Lamps
  - A church and houses in front of a body of water., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref16; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Lakes; Water; Churches; Religious Sites; Buildings; North America; Bridges; Landscapes
  - A landscape image of a bridge over a body of water., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref17; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Forest/Woodlands; Water; Bridges; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Landscapes
  - Men standing on a balcony overlooking machinery (linked ref109)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref18; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 X 9.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Machines; Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Factories
  - Men standing and sitting on the edge of a canal lock., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref19; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Canals; Water; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Dams/Barrages
  - A drawbridge in mid-movement., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref20; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America
  - A metal structure., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref21; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.4 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Bridges